question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Toronto is the capital city of the North American country of Canada.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is refered to as &quot;The Shape&quot;.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The sum of any two odd integers is odd.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "New Haven is the capital city of the state of Connecticut in the United States.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The French Kingdom helped the United States gain their independence over Great Britain during the Revolutionary War.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Rhode Island is actually located on the US mainland, despite its name.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Rabbits can see what&#039;s behind themselves without turning their heads.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
